<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Weazel News RP</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Weazel News RP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LSPD Under Fire!!!</title><link>/posts/lspd-under-fire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/lspd-under-fire/</guid><description>Last night the Law Firm of Trust, LLP served the LSPD. The claim stated that the law firm was representing the locals of Los Santos in a class action law suit against the LSPD. Weazel News was able to uncover that over twenty-two locals were signed on to the suit with more yet to be confirmed or named. The claim went on further to state that the LSPD was being charged with several acts of reckless driving, wonton disregard for public safety, and a general lack of value towards locals life.</description></item><item><title>The Weazely Impersonation at the LSPD</title><link>/posts/weazely-impersonator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/weazely-impersonator/</guid><description>This afternoon a report came in that a Weazel News van driven by one Opie pulled up to the LSPD building and a second person in the van opened fire on two police officers, Farva and Brown. Officer Farva was able to stun Jackson using his taser while Opie was able to drive off. The two police officers gave chase and when Opie attempted to lose his followers down an alley way instead found himself stuck and proceeded to open fire upon the officers.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 09:44:07 -0600</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Weazel News RP strives to capture the hard hitting stories that are impacting the citizens of Los Santos. If you have a story you&amp;rsquo;d like Weazel News RP to investigate please contact the editor at the Weazel News Offices within Los Santos.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity to actual persons, living or dead, or actual events, is purely coincidental.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 09:44:07 -0600</pubDate><guid>/contributing/</guid><description>Weazel News RP strives to capture the hard hitting stories that are impacting the citizens of Los Santos. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in contributing content to Weazel News RP then you&amp;rsquo;re in the correct place. This page exists as a guideline for how to write, format, and submit your articles for consideration. Please note that not all articles received will be published and that it is up to the Weazel News RP editorial staff to make the final decision.</description></item><item><title>Homelessness Plagues the City</title><link>/posts/homelessness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/homelessness/</guid><description>At the beginning of this piece Weazel News wanted to learn more about the state of homelessness in the Los Santo&amp;rsquo;s. We wanted to understand what brought the people to the state of being homeless and how the city could step up as a community and help solve the problem. What we didn&amp;rsquo;t expect is the wide range of answers and opinions on the topic as well as the stories we heard from all walks of life.</description></item><item><title>Shots Fired at LSPD</title><link>/posts/shots-fired-at-lspd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/shots-fired-at-lspd/</guid><description>Yesterday reports came in of shots being fired on or near the Olympic Freeway near the LSPD. Witnesses in the area stated that they were standing near the LSPD station building when up to six shots were heard coming from the direction of the freeway. Shortly thereafter officers were dispatched and came to investigate. During their investigation a vehicle pulled up to the front of the LSPD and a one Keebo Pratt approached the reporter on site and started to share a story about the LSPD.</description></item><item><title>Welcome Home</title><link>/posts/welcome-to-weazel-rp-news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/welcome-to-weazel-rp-news/</guid><description>Welcome to the new home of Weazel RP News the source for updates about the city of Los Santos - Legit RP.</description></item></channel></rss>