<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Los Santos on Weazel News RP</title><link>/tags/los-santos/</link><description>Recent content in Los Santos on Weazel News RP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/los-santos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Firetruck Mayhem on Elgin Avenue</title><link>/posts/firetruck-mayhem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/firetruck-mayhem/</guid><description>This afternoon a firetruck was taken by a local Motor Cycle gang. Allegedly Opie Winston and Jaxson Teller obtained the fire truck at the south LSFD dispatch building. They proceeded to take the firetuck on a joy ride along Elgin Ave. where the LSPD proceeded to take chase. While attempting to stop the vehicle Weazel News was able to track the truck along Elgin until it reached the intersection of Vespucci Blvd.</description></item><item><title>A Fishy Business in the City</title><link>/posts/a-fishy-business-in-the-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/a-fishy-business-in-the-city/</guid><description>Yesterday the citizens participated in a fishy competition set forth by the Mayor of Los Santos. All citizens interested in winning a cash prize were welcomed to spend two days casting their rods and hopes into the water to try and earn the most points through catching seasonal fish that had recently and temporarily migrated into the waters around Los Santos. To make things as fair as possible the Mayor declared that the fishing competition would be split across two days to give all citizens of all work schedules an opportunity to participate.</description></item><item><title>Gone in 60 Seconds, Los Santos Style</title><link>/posts/racing-comes-to-los-santos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/racing-comes-to-los-santos/</guid><description>There was a lot of demand in the city for an opportunity for those with a lead foot and a desire to have their hair blown back for the citizenry to race. That time as come as racing has come to the city of Los Santos! Yesterday, the Mayor and his staff announced that the very first track, The Hollywood Hills, was opened in the city with sanctioned races, betting, winners and losers.</description></item><item><title>One Mans Journey Home</title><link>/posts/one-mans-journey-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/one-mans-journey-home/</guid><description>Recently our reporting team had the pleasure of being intruduced to an interesting citizen of Los Santos. Quirky, shy, and always willing to help Arturo Campo was on a journey tod find his way home and we here at Weazel News felt it was a journey worth sharing. We first met Arturo, a thirty-six (36) year old Los Santo&amp;rsquo;s native, in the tent city under the Olympic Freeway. He was sitting in a camping chair and mostly seemed just excited to speak with someone.</description></item><item><title>The Weazely Impersonation at the LSPD</title><link>/posts/weazely-impersonator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/weazely-impersonator/</guid><description>This afternoon a report came in that a Weazel News van driven by one Opie pulled up to the LSPD building and a second person in the van opened fire on two police officers, Farva and Brown. Officer Farva was able to stun Jackson using his taser while Opie was able to drive off. The two police officers gave chase and when Opie attempted to lose his followers down an alley way instead found himself stuck and proceeded to open fire upon the officers.</description></item><item><title>Homelessness Plagues the City</title><link>/posts/homelessness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/homelessness/</guid><description>At the beginning of this piece Weazel News wanted to learn more about the state of homelessness in the Los Santo&amp;rsquo;s. We wanted to understand what brought the people to the state of being homeless and how the city could step up as a community and help solve the problem. What we didn&amp;rsquo;t expect is the wide range of answers and opinions on the topic as well as the stories we heard from all walks of life.</description></item></channel></rss>